Barack and Michelle Obama's daughter, Malia, has debuted a new name, Malia Ann.
She said, you know, I want to be on my own merit out here as her Hollywood career heats up.
She's distancing herself from the former president and first lady.
She's saying that she, at 25, has decided to drop her last name
to prevent being a Nepo baby and carve her own path.
Okay.
I mean, I had a different name for 10 years.
Amanda Deva.
It's on my degree.
That's how committed I was.
Wow.
Okay.
We, though, wanted to talk about some names that some people may not want to shake off,
but other names that people may have been like, you know what?
I'm all on that.
Now, if you're rocking around with the Cosby last name, that is going to get you one of these.
What about Huxtable?
Huxtable?
Huxtable will get you one of these.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If your last name is Thomas, I feel like you need to be very clear in saying no relation to Clarence.
Oh, man.
No relation to Clarence.
All right.
What if your last name is Baldwin?
I might change my last name to Baldwin.
I would love to be out here.
Hi, I'm Amanda Baldwin.
Yes.
Amanda Baldwin.
And they're like, oh, are you related?
I like to think so.
What if your last name is Jackson?
Regardless of which Jackson you're related to, Michael, Jesse, Reggie, you are the descendant of a slave owner.
That is a fact.
We are, we are, we are.
We are, we are.
That is a fact.